Oh man, I just love Christmas cookies.
We know beach. We can tell because you
weigh 437 lbs.
Uncle Chuck. Hey,
Uncle Chuck. Where is your trailer?
Damn. Uncle Chuck, looks like someone
straight up stole your house.
>> Bro, stop smiling. It's not funny.
You can't stay with us tonight, Uncle
Chuck. It's times like this where
hedgehogs must band together. Oh no, he
ain't, bro. We are not letting someone
from a trailer park stay in our house on
Christmas.
>> You're a freaking psycho man. Get your
hands off of me before I lay your fat
ass out. Okay, hold it, [__] It's not
Manic's fault you parked in a black
neighborhood. Let's just make like a
pair of balls and bounce, bro. Suddenly,
I get the feeling our dear old uncle
doesn't want us around. Yes, my bro.
It's clear that he does not welcome our
kindness and gratitude.
Bro, what? Bro, why is there a trailer
parked in our backyard? I don't know
what you're talking about. Damn it, bro.
You stole Uncle Chuck's trailer.
No, I know. You know what? Yeah, that I
did steal his trailer. And no one's
going to find out about it, fat boy.
Especially Mama. Are you insane? Mama
isn't just going to ignore an $800
trailer in the backyard.
>> Is that me trailer?
>> No, it's these nuts in your mouth.
>> Uncle Chuck, why don't you come inside
and have dinner with us?
the money
>> here. Bartleby, I know Christmas is
tomorrow, but I wanted to give you
something early. Uh-huh. Why? Do my eyes
deceive me? Or is that a Ferrer rich
chocolate? [__] you really pulled out
all the stops this year? I reckon you
had to break open your piggy bank just
to afford this, did you not?
>> Yes, but I did it for you. Do you see
how it's covered in gold foil?
>> Yes, [__] I see. That's how you know
it's for rich people.
Bart Levy, don't you like your Christmas
present?
>> It is adequate. My [__] you needn't
worry yourself.
>> Calm your dits, bro. You know the rules.
Nobody eats until we join hands and say
grace.
>> I don't do that.
>> I'm thankful for all of this wonderful
food. lovingly handcrafted by my mommy
who loves me so very much. But most
importantly, I'm grateful for Bartalby,
my lover, who could be anywhere else
tonight, yet chose to be here with me on
the day of Jesus's birth.
>> I'm grateful you [__] got toilet
paper in the bathroom cuz God knows I'm
going to drop a massive dump out of my
fat butt after I get done with the mac
and cheese.
>> Why you want thankful for? Nobody cares,
old man. Just say what you have to say
and go.
>> Manic, be nice. He didn't mean it,
Charles. Yeah, he did. It's Manic. Why
are you lying, mama?
>> You know what? I'm out. I promised my
great grandfather I would help him bake
some pies in our paid off house.
There is no point in
cool. Get out of our house, [__]
>> Haha. Damn, bro. Leave some food for the
rest of us. You fat [__]
>> You don't believe this. That will get me
out of trailer. Who's out there? Get
away from my trailer.
Huh? Well, well, well. What a welcome
surprise. If it isn't the uncle of my
arch nemesis, Sonic the Hedgehog. Dr.
Robotney. What are you doing in me
trailer? Um, I think you mean my
trailer. Your nephew Manic traded it to
me for the new Call of Duty game. Sleep
bingo. Get your asses over here. I want
you to laugh at Uncle Chuck with me. You
see this trailer used to belong to him
and it is because of yours truly that he
at without house and home on Christmas
day. Thingo go in the bathroom and
unclog the toilet. Daddy has to poop
again.
Lingo, here's another one in case that
one gets stuck in his poop.
Why are you still here? Didn't you just
hear me say that I'm going to go poop?
There's the mobility scooter over there
that I stole from you 4 months ago. I'll
give it to you if you trade me the
whitey tighties you are wearing right
now. Oh, you know we wear white because
I know you Charles and only the truest
of men wear whitey tighties. Men like me
where only the softest of cotton is
allowed to touch my balls.
Poor Uncle Chuck. Hopefully he likes
these mashed potatoes we brought him.
Food always cheers me up.
I [__] hate my life. Knuckles the
cool kid shouldn't be living like this.
Is that Knuckles? Since when did
Knuckles live in a trailer?
>> Sup, [__] Didn't expect to see your
asses here. What's those mashed potatoes
for? I don't live here in this trailer
park, by the way. So, don't go give any
[__] the wrong idea.
>> Knuckles, why didn't you tell us you
live in a trailer park?
>> I just said I don't live here. Knuckles,
come inside and help me finish baking
the pecan pie without pecans since we
don't have enough money to afford nuts.
[__] My homeboy, my best friend in the
whole world lives in a dumb trailer. All
while I was trashing Uncle Chuck for the
same thing. What have I done? It's not
your fault, bro. You had no idea. But
maybe, just maybe, this will help you
reconsider your actions.
Evening, Uncle Chuck. I heard about your
trailer that really sucks some major
balls.
>> Thanks, Bart.
>> No, I saw it driving down the street. I
thought it was you, so I didn't think
anything of it. Then I remembered your
driver's license is revoked. Sorry, man.
It's okay.
>> Honey, look. That man is asking for
donations for the children's homeless
shelter. Ho ho ho. Would you like to
donate some money to some kids in need?
Kind, sir.
>> Why in God's name would I want to do
that, [__] What have homeless kids
ever done for me? I work at Taco Bell.
>> Well, damn, sir. You have a really big
butt. If you want to quit your day job
and come work in my toy shop and stay at
the North Pole.
>> Are you looking at my butt?
>> Eyes off the goods, pal. Do you want me
to beat you up? I go to the YMCA. You
know, Uncle Chuck, Christmas isn't only
about material possessions. It's about
what you are willing to give.
>> Why don't you go give them this quarter?
>> You would be surprised, Charles, with
how even the tiniest act of generosity
can change someone else's world.
>> Ho ho ho. Every little bit helps.
Master Bartley, shall I present Mr.
Charles with his Christmas gift now of
$1 million?
>> No, Alfred. Christmas present are for
good boys and girls, not Uncle Shuck.
>> Hey, hey, hey,
hey.
in fact.
>> So, you're telling me that you're the
uncle of Sonic the Hedgehog, the main
character of Sonic Underground, which
got cancelled after only 40 episodes,
and you think that's something to be
proud of. No wonder you're riding around
on that yeast scooter. Hey, son. How you
liking this beat, my boy? It's pretty
[__] and pops. Take in the music, boy.
Take it all in. This is the type of
music you beat your wife to.
>> Daddy, who is that strange man outside?
Does he want to listen to Sonic
underground music, too?
>> Snack kicks. Isn't that the same from
the donation fund? Did he follow us all
the way from the Target Superstore?
>> Yeah, I think it is. Just ignore him.
I'm not about to judge a guy who has
tastes as good as Sonic Underground
music.
What the hell? The car is moving on its
own. Somebody help us.
Daddy, there's a train coming. We have
to get off the train tracks or we are
[__] dead.
>> Come on, sweetie. Let's get out of here.
Why did you lock the door?
>> This car cost me $500. If the car
doesn't make it out alive, neither will
we. Hey, you come over. He ran. Give us
a push.
Is he coming?
>> No, he's just backing the [__] up. I
don't want to die, daddy. [__] will
you shut up? We are [__]
What the That's Michael Huxen.
Look everyone, Michael Jackson is saving
the kid by getting him out of the middle
of the road.
It's sorry we don't have any more for
you to steal.
Actually, we brought you some mashed
potatoes. Uncle Chuck, it was wrong of
me to steal your trailer. Why don't you
come back home with us? We still have
some leftovers you can have.
So, no, you want me
for dinner and it's leftovers.
My preetic.
>> You're a [__] Yeah, we tried to be
nice to you, old man. But if you're
going to be a big fat baby about it,
then we'll just take these potatoes
home.
>> Great grandfather. Why do people who
love each other fight on Christmas?
>> I don't know, Knuckles. Come help me dig
around four candles in the neighbor's
dumpster since we can't afford to pay
the electricity bill. I'm cold because I
had to sell all of my clothes to buy you
those beans. Okay, you want to
say bitching?
Of course, Uncle Chuck. We love you.
Uncle Chuck, I think it's time I finally
come out and say it.
>> You better not be.
>> I was the one who stole your trailer,
Uncle Chuck.
I thought you deserved it for how often
you mean to us. I'm really really sorry.
>> Okay.
will hit us.
>> No, you probably wondering what I'm
thankful for. I'm thankful for your
thank you enough for this, Bartleby. It
was the wish of every single kid in the
Makea-Wish Foundation to meet you
specifically on their final day here on
Earth. It's good to know the last thing
they'll see before they die as you.
Well, it's as I always say, if there's
one thing I love besides my [__] and
money is the beautiful laughter of
children. That is so nice. Please go
inside.
>> You're not Bart Levy. You are just a fat
guy.
>> Where is Bart Levy? Well, well, you see
Bar Bart, you couldn't make it today.
>> Huh?
Damn it, Bart Lebby. You paid me $100 to
do this because you said you were too
busy to visit these kids on Christmas.
You knew they would see through my
disguise because I'm fat. You were just
setting those kids up for
disappointment. Also, you could surprise
them with glee by showing up yourself
moments later.
>> Perhaps you are right, fool. And what
has occurred cannot be changed, no
matter how much you cry like a baby.
Now, step aside. Me and my [__] stopped
by Dunkin Donuts to surprise those Make
a Wish kids before they die. Oh, Bart
Lebby, you're here. Doctor, what is
wrong? Bart Lebby, I don't know how to
say this. While you were out in the
hall, I'm afraid every one of those kids
died from their cancer. This is all my
fault. The shock of seeing me instead of
Bart Lebby was too much for their poor
little hearts.
>> No, everyone, it's not one's fault here
today. You see, unfortunately, these
kind of things happen. But it's not the
end of the world. And if we let
ourselves fall apart over something this
small, then what are we really besides a
group of sexy, handsome men with huge
balls?
>> Barty. Doctor, I don't understand. I
thought you said all of the kids died
from cancer. It would seem that his
desire to see you was so powerful. It
was enough to cure his cancer for some
reason.
>> Only you have that kind of power. Barty.
>> Okay. Who wants donuts?
Who is that hobby? Before you help
yourself to these donuts, how would you
like to make a little trade?
Oh, hello Uncle Chuck. Sonic, MC
Knuckles, and I decorated the inside of
your trailer for Christmas. Man
especially felt really awful for what he
had done.
>> Don't you know how much electricity
cost
a
>> Uncle Chuck? Why don't you look behind
the Christmas tree over
>> Yeah, Uncle Chuck, please.
>> Let me guess.
Uncle Chuck, don't think so of us.
>> It's your Christmas present, Uncle
Chuck.
>> From all of us to you.
No, Charles, you're not the worst. A
truly terrible angle would leave things
as they are. And if there's one thing I
learned after all these years, it's that
you are the sweetest, kindest man I have
ever known.
>> Dare I say, you have always been more of
a father to me than I ever was.
>> Yeah, me too.
Uncle Chuck, you found our present.
>> That's reality.
Bart, lety help me. Shut up, [__] It's
every man for himself. Hurry, everybody
head for the overpass. Says there are
>> Oh my god, somebody help me.
>> Oh my god, Batman. That boy is being
taken away by the tornado.
And we save him. Where?
>> I don't believe it. Our house is gone.
>> Well, believe it simp because it's
happening. And this is so uncool. How
can a home just be taken away like that?
You really mean that, Uncle Chuck?
world.
>> You will be surprised, Charles, with how
even the tiniest act of generosity can
change someone else's world.
Well, it's not our house, but it's not
half bad. Maybe this is what Christmas
is about. Not money or any of that [__]
It's about friends and family.
Your ref starting to hit it.
You don't believe it. It's And look,
Knuckles is there, too. You [__]
aren't going to believe who saved my fat
ass. This is the real life Santa Claus.
>> Mr. Santa Claus here. He's supposed
back then.
>> Mo Charles, I want you to keep that $48.
>> Oh my god, he knows the exact amount. He
really is Santa Claus.
>> You need the money more than homeless
babies because you don't have a lot of
[__] And also because with the help
from Bart Levy, you were able to
discover the true meaning of Christmas.
In fact, if you want me to show you my
appreciation, I can let you have a
little alone time with one of my cute
little elves. Oh, hello there. I didn't
see you. Yeah, you behind the computer
screen. You got one fat butt.
I hope you had a nice Christmas this
year. I pray to God that your next one
will be even better.
>> Hey everybody, why don't you all hop
into my golden limousine and we can
drive around looking at Christmas
lights? It will be my treat.
>> Oh, hello there. I didn't see you. Were
you following Uncle Chuck AROUND ALL
DAY?
>> YEAH, BABY. YEAH,
>> that's pretty weird. Yes, you are quite
right indeed. His posterior is
exceptionally large.
>> Oh yeah,
>> I am impressed by your restraint. Most
people I know would have been tempted to
give it a good smack or two. By the way,
for a limited time, only if you joined
Hey 12345's Patreon, you can download a
really cool wallpaper of me. Thank you
very much.
>> No, thank you for commenting, liking,
and subscribing. Just know that the
wallpaper is shaped like a square. So
when you do set it as a desktop
background, it will look kind of shitty.
But hey, that's what we're working with
here.
Never never give up.
Never give up the fight.
No matter how tough it gets for us, I
know we can make it through.
As long as we keep standing working
together.
Go ahead and go with your best shot. Try
anything you want to. Nothing's coming.
We can make it better.
Come on now.
Never never give up.
Never give up.
Never give up the fight. We'll never
give up the fight.
Never give up the fight.
We'll never give UP THE FIGHT.
NEVER NEVER GIVE UP.
Never give up the fight.
Never never give up.
No matter how tough it gets for us, I
know we can make it through.
As long as we keep standing tall,
working